[ Watch on kissFlix.co ]
This is strange…
I’ve got a bad feeling…
Same, Rudi… It’s unusual.
Last time, it felt the same.
Right before that accident…
Do you think… any others?
I think so!
After that, we never saw the bodies
who died in the accidents.
It's complicated Bayu…
But…
This time it felt different.
By the way, Rudi…
Where is Heru?
I haven't seen him today?
No idea!
Bayu!
What?
Wait, let me check.
What's wrong here?
Oji? Oji!
-Bayu, help me!
-Oji…
Bayu!
Oji!
Take the bodyใ
-I't hot, so hot!
-Take the soulใ
Take the lifeใ
Oji!
Mom?
Yes…
Take it first
so your blood pressure won’t go up!
I know.
Then, you'll be better!
Take it first.
-Yuda.
-Yes?
Your drink.
Since when are you
this concerned about me…
What’s going on?
Why is this one never-ending, huh?
If Dad were here,
maybe things would’ve been faster…
You know right, he is the master!
I know!
Talking about Dad…
I kinda miss him!
It's feels like forever
since he has been back.
Yeah, he didn't give any updates lately.
I miss him too!
Well, maybe he’s chasing
the deadlines there.
But if he comes home…
Someone’s gonna have it easy.
That guy! Freedom!
You happy?
Mom, it’s okay!
Just let Dad come home quickly.
-Happy?
-Of course I’m happy!
-You Lazy!
-Hey, I could get a day off too!
-You lazy!
-Hey, that’s slander…
That's a slander, Mom!
-Go with your friend…
-You slander!
Yuda!
It's because you
keep grumbling!
-Yuda?
-What?
That… Heru's car.
-Dad?
-Is he back?
Mr. Heru? Sir?
Mr. Heru!
What brings you here this late, Sir?
Where is he? I really miss him, Sir!
-Where is he? Dad?
-Yuda!
Bayu…
He is dead.
-Laras?
-Mom?
-No way!
-Mom…
Laras!
Sir…
Sir, don’t be joking
in front of Laras and Mom.
-I'm not joking!
-Please…
Where did you get that information from?
Work accident.
Then what?
If it's true, what about the body?
Was there a body, Sir?
The body was gone, Yuda…
Swept away by the sea.
And then?
What step did you take? Just stay quiet?
Call the SAR team, call the police!
Find my Dad!
Find his body if he's gone!
Call whoever it is!
Wherever he is now, find him!
We've tried so hard.
-Try? What "try"?
-How could he have died?
How could he die?
Tell me, Sir!
-How could he have died?
-We truly apologize!
S-Sir, please bring him back!
Dad!
Dad, you should come back!
Why don't you find him?
Bayu!
-Dad!
-Martha!
Mom!
Yuda, help!
In the midst of positive news regarding
the Suramadu Bridge mega project,
cases of child abductions have been
increasingly reported over the past year.
They have occurred once again
near the project site…
A 10-year-old girl has been declared
missing after playing in the project area.
Local authorities confirm…
That investigations are still ongoing,
including a review of previous case data.
However, amid this wave of reports…
The contractors are actively bringing
in large numbers of new workers
from outside the city,
In an effort to accelerate
the completion of the project.
You sure you'll take Mom
to the project site?
Why not just stay here
and focus on taking care of her?
I'm sure.
Also…
This is all for our future.
For who? You?
Is she only my responsibility, huh?
Five years!
I’ve been killing myself
taking care of her.
I never asked anyone for help… and you?
Meanwhile you got to study
and live like a normal person, didn’t you?
I also have dreams, Yuda!
But look…
I buried all my dreams deep down.
I always gave way because you once said…
There would be a time
when it would be my turn, now what?
-Where is it?
-Don't you realize?
That place is dangerous.
I went there…
To prove that he was murdered, sacrificed,
offered up for the Project Sacrifice!
I don’t want anything to happen
to you or Mom…
I’m going to prove whether the rumors
about the project sacrifices are real!
True or false, those rumors won’t change
anything in our family!
Right now, Mom should come first right?
Now look what you have done?
And yet you took a job
from a dangerous place…
Just to uncover the truth about Dad?
So,
what's wrong with that?
So what's wrong with me working there too!
At least for my own future.
Who the hell are they?
Who's coming?
Just come and go like the owner.
New worker?
Be careful.
-I can do this.
-Be careful.
Thank you, Sir.
-Alright.
-Oh My!
You even brought your sick mother here…
This has become a real problem.
Who are you?
-I'm Yuda, Sir.
-Thank you.
This is my mother and my sister, Laras.
Introdu- Introduce me, I'm Yanto.
Greetings! My full name is Yanto.
I'm a security guard in this apartment.
You will be in room 506.
I’ll guide you there…
Mr. Yanto, here is the luggage.
How dare you call me "Mister"!
Take care of your mom!
They brought a lot stuff huh!?
Well, here are the rules
for residents of the apartment.
Please read them carefully
and pay close attention.
First, don't be noisy!
Don't dare to play loud music
like 'a boom boom car'.
Wait, these are too heavy!
Listen to my instructions first.
Done? Okay.
Next, it is prohibited
to bring other people here…
Friends, family…
Except for your mother, she's allowed
to stay to take care of her!
Next,
by 10 p.m. everyone must already
be inside their respective rooms.
No one is allowed to go out.
Whether it’s to the shop for cigarettes,
soap, or even sanitary pads. You can't.
All these rules are made
for everyone’s comfort and safety.
Please understand,
that this is a project site, after all.
But the apartment
really is empty, isn’t it?
There are no people here!
It's not empty, Yuda.
Not many have come back yet.
It’s shift change time.
Anyway, all these rules for comf--
Mom!
What happened?
Oh My, how could this happen?
-Mom!
-Mom?
Mom, what's wrong?
Mom, what's wrong? Mom!
-What's wrong with her?
-Mom!
What's wrong with her?
Mom!
-Mom, Yuda here!
-Please forgive me God!
-Mom, Laras and Yuda are here with you.
-Ask forgiveness.
Laras and Yuda are here with you.
-You okay, Mom?
-Yes.
That's ridiculous!
Yuda.
I'm here, Mom!
What's wrong?
Alright, let's get
to the room immediately!
G-Get some ice-…h-hot water, I mean.
So your mother could relax!
I understand, it’s a new place.
So it's normal!
She’s probably just a bit shocked!
It's just the beginning…
Can't it just wait a moment…please!
What was it called?
But it's on each floor…
So we guarantee it would be safe.
Yuda, Yuda… Wait Yuda!
This is your mother’s wheelchair.
So, she won’t get tired.
Oh My, it's so heavy!
Here, here Ma'am!
Just step back slowly, Ma'am!
Wait…
Be careful!
Yuda, you take care of her.
I'll carry your things.
Yanto!
Is this building
really this sparsely occupied?
B-But it’s not like
there are no residents…
Since the old tenant left…
People around here
just won't to stay there.
Maybe because it’s in the corner…
So, no one chooses it anymore.
Alright Mom, I'll take care of your feet.
Be careful to carry her.
Relax, Mom.
Alright, here we are at the fifth floor!
Here is the room.
If the windows are dirty,
you clean them yourselves.
Who the hell left
their laundry hanging here?
Please come in.
Please.
Where’s the switch for this thing?
Ah, it works.
Come in!
Make yourself at home.
It’s a bit dusty, yeah…
but just clean it up.
Oh right, here is the key, Yuda!
Yes.
-Your "train" key!
-Train?
Oh, people from Medan
call a "train" a motorcycle.
Clean it up, tidy it nicely--
treat it like your own home,
just don’t burn it.
-Okay?
-Thank you, Sir.
My pleasure.
Yuda!
If she's here,
does she miss Dad even more?
She even did it at home, Laras.
Keeps talking in her sleep.
No difference!
He used to work at this site…it's normal.
But I feel like it’s getting worse here.
Getting worse.
So I'm worried about her…
Alright!
Then we need to focus
on taking care of her.
Things are different now.
Just hope your decision
doesn’t end up holding me back.
What did you say?
Holding you back?
What do you mean?
Right now, Mom comes first.
I can still take care of her, by the way!
I won't be "holding you back"!
Mom is just your excuse.
You just don’t want me and Mom
to be here. Am I right?
-That’s not what I mean.
-Then what?
I don't und…Tell me then!
What’s actually going on in your head
I don't get it!
What?
Follow me!
Come on.
You want to know? Come!
Five years, Laras!
Five years I was chasing these!
MISSING PERSON - SURABAYA
In 2004, right around the time Dad died,
there were reports
of workers disappearing…
In Surabaya…
And Madura.
MISSING PEOPLE IN MADURA
Right?
Fourteen people! It's fourteen!
He must be one of them.
And there’s still no clarity!
Every year, people go missing--
and it keeps getting covered up.
But it feels odd.
Every missing worker happens…
It happened around the night of Suro.
And I don’t understand
what the connection is.
This is strange, Laras.
It doesn't make sense!
WELCOME TO THE BRIDGE PROJECT
YOU ARE ENTERING MANDATORY PPE AREA
Go on!
Slow down or you’ll get hit!
Come forward!
Come forward and turn right.
Yeah.
Good afternoon, Mr. Yuda.
Here is a PPE helmet for you.
-Hold on!
-Sure, Sir.
-Thank you.
-Please, Sir.
So, how is it, any issues here?
For this site, right now
we’re facing an issue with cable stray.
But it’s not significant.
Progress is still ongoing.
Soon you will see in this site.
-Let me check it first.
-Alright Sir, thank you.
-Afternoon, Sir.
-Afternoon.
I’m Yuda, the new construction supervisor.
-Who?
-Yuda.
Oh, okay.
What’s going on here? Any problems?
It’s normal, an uneven tensioning!
The cable tension
keeps fluctuating and is not stable.
Their calculations were off, Sir?
Well, maybe you're right.
It happened a few times this month.
Sir?
This shouldn’t be caused by wind.
Here, Sir.
Rudi!
Let’s check the pylon control room!
Sure.
I’ve already informed Mr. Rudi.
If wind tension readings are normal,
maybe the main issue
lies in the core foundation piles.
Yuda!
This is a national project, Yuda!
We’re on a strict deadline, you know!
If we never try, when we can know?
I brought you here because
I thought you were smart, Yuda.
Pile installation and other works
did fail at times.
But everything was completed
without spending time on research.
If so, may I ask you a question?
How were the previous issues
resolved, Sir?
For instance…
During the pile installation failure.
How did you handle it?
Reports of abductions around
the project site have occurred again.
A six year old child is reported missing
while playing near the coastline.
To this day, police remain confused
regarding the motive behind the abduction.
With the increasing number
of missing children cases this month…
Over the years,
children kept disappearing…
Yet none have ever been found.
Authorities urge the public
to remain cautious,
as child abduction cases
are still considered to be occurring
frequently over the past year…
In the name of the Father,
the Son, and the Holy Spirit…
Mary was told by the angel of the Lord
she would conceive by the Holy Spirit.
Hail Mary, full of grace,
the Lord is with thee…
Blessed are you among women, and
blessed is the fruit of your womb, Jesus.
Holy Mary, Mother of God…
Pray for us sinners,
now and at the hour of our death.
Amen.
Yes.
Rini, is she absent?
Yeah…
Laras, can you back up Rini's task?
She didn’t come in today.
Help input today’s steel construction data
going into the dock. Can you?
Sure.
Alright, you can stay there and maybe…
you’ll even find a match there!
From the project workers too!
Hey, don’t date a project man!
They’ve got too many wives yet so poor.
Hey!
Don't say that!
Alright everyone, keep going!
Oh, you live in the apartment too?
Yeah.
Maybe we can watch the sea view from
the rooftop sometime; it's pretty nice!
By the way…
I actually have the rooftop key.
Yes. Okay.
Thanks, Wati.
I'm leaving now.
Yeah.
SURAMADU BRIDGE PROJECT
PERSONNEL DATA 2004
NAME - POSITION - HOMETOWN
Dad?
Laras!
Go, go, go now!
Hurry.
Laras!
Hey, who’s that near there?
Oh My God!
Hey, watch out!
Hey, hey, hey!
Whose cable there?
Laras! Get out, get out!
Get out of the way!
What happened?
Hey, hey, are you okay?
What?
Let's move this.
-Move it.
-We're trying.
I told you, this is a dangerous place!
Mom?
We're home!
Yuda! Yuda, Mom is gone!
Mom is gone, Mom is gone!
Stop joking, Laras!
I am not!
How could she?
Laras! How could she be gone?
Where is she?
How could I know
when I'm with you all this time?
But you said…
Fine, you stay here.
I'm gonna check outside, okay? Stay here!
She doesn’t know the way--
and she’s in a wheelchair…
-Mom?
-Mom!
Mom!
Laras, you can check around this floor.
I'll go downstairs!
Mom!
Mom?
Mom, you here?
Damn!
Mom!
Mom, where are you?
Mom?
Mom!
This isn't real!
This isn't real! This isn't real!
Not real! Not real!
-Laras? Laras?
-Our Father, who art in heaven…
Give us this day our daily bread,
and forgive us our trespasses,
as we forgive those
who trespass against us…
-Laras?
-…but free us from evil…
Laras?
Laras!
Our Father, who art in heaven…
-…be done on earth, as it is in heaven…
-Laras!
Hey, hey! It's me!
Yuda!
Yeah.
Yes.
Hey, calm down!
Calm down!
You can tell me later!
Mom, where is she?
Please calm down!
I searched downstairs,
but I couldn’t find her!
Did you find her?
I can’t find her, Yuda!
Where she's gone then?
Yuda!
Yanto!
Please help me. Please!
Why do you look just seen a ghost?
Wait.
Your mother… leaving the apartment?
Look!
How could she… stand up by herself?
Hey!
There.
Looks like she went to rooftop.
No one can go up there…
-Mom?
-The rooftop’s locked.
Mom!
-Let's go!
-Mom!
What are you doing?
Hey!
You came to scare me and then vanish, huh!
Come on, Laras!
Mom!
Quick, Sir!
It's locked!
-Damn, it's locked!
-Let me try!
Push again, Push!
-Push again!
-Yuda!
Here, I have the key!
Alright, open it!
Mom!
-Mom!
-Mom.
-Mom, you okay?
-There are a lot of children!
-Many children--
Those poor children!
-Those poor children!
-Whose children?
-They are innocent!
-Mom?
-They're not supposed to die.
-Mom!
-Whose children?
Those poor children!
Bayu!
Those…
Those children…
Those children… they’re innocent!
This is Intan, my daughter.
She went missing not long ago.
I’m sure she disappeared near the site.
But she's not the only one.
In the past few months…
Suddenly, more children have been missing
none of them have been found.
Missing?
Have you called the police?
It won't work…
Even the cases
all over the news go nowhere.
What chance do I have?
I have nothing!
Has your husband
been looking for Intan too?
He passed away a long time ago.
Right after he warned me
about the project sacrifices.
I’m sure… he became one of them.
I-I won’t let that happen to Intan…
I know your mother knows something.
Excuse me, Wati…
What is your husband’s name?
Parwis.
Your husband’s name is on here…marked
Just like our father’s, Bayu.
NAME - POSITION - HOMETOWN
What do you mean?
Your father died five years ago
just like my husband?
Yes.
He died in the early phase of construction
when they drove
the first foundation piles.
Laras, where did you find this?
In the old records room.
I took it because…
I think It might be
connected to Dad’s death.
I remember…
My husband lost
during the Petik Laut ritual!
On the night of Satu Suro.
I have a feeling,
it’s going to happen again this year.
Impossible!
Yuda!
Satu Suro is in two days.
We have to do something, Laras.
If what she said was true…
We can prove Dad was sacrificed
by the greedy people.
There.
Look up! Here…
The cable tension readings
are slightly below normal.
Why do we keep making mistakes?
-But everything matches the data…
-Yeah.
-Just add it.
-Add!
Excuse me, Sir.
By calculation,
the tension should already be a match.
If we add it,
the cables could over-tighten in the cold.
You think so? Then what do you suggest?
Yeah, it's up to you, Sir!
If you don’t want to follow… That's okay.
I’d be very interested to see
how you handle this.
Hey!
Damn!
Hey, what should we do?
Everyone back! Call the ambulance!
Please help!
Sir.
Everyone, move back!
Be careful! Look up!
Hello, Sir?
How are the preparations
for the Petik Laut ritual, Sir?
Alright, thank you, Sir.
The worker…
Yesterday… How's he now?
Man…he is wrecked!
How about his family?
You know,
when someone die in this project…
The news would soon disappear!
Here, the dead get nothing.
They never return their bodies
to the family.
I don't get it, it's always like this.
It just a rumour.
Attention!
Due to the Petik Laut ritual
taking place tonight.
Work will end early today.
All non-essential personnel
are to leave the site immediately.
May this ritual ensure
the smooth progress of our work.
The ritual is ready.
It's all just a cover
to hide the real ritual.
What about my daughter?
Take them!
Take it!
Let's go!
Mom, you were
talking in your sleep last night.
You miss Dad again, don’t you?
I miss him too, Mom.
But, Dad’s gone.
You have to stay strong, okay?
Now, you’re all I have, Mom.
I can’t lose you too.
-Mom?
-Does it hurt?
Mom, I'm home!
Yuda is home.
Wait…
Mom, what are you doing here?
Where is Laras?
Why?
You want to eat?
Alright, you can ask me. I'll help you!
I promise, I'll accompany you, Mom!
I'll give you everything you want!
Laras, what's wrong?
Yuda, Yuda…Look!
I-I saw…
-What was it?
-I-I…
Alright, calm down!
It's fine, nothing happened.
It's okay, let's get out!
Let's go!
Mom!
Yuda… I-I saw--
-I saw--
-Nothing happened, Laras.
It's nothing, okay?
There’s something more important.
I saw children…
being taken into the site just now.
-Children?
-Yes, I almost get caught.
I’m going to prove it.
Not the site…
But administrative office.
There’s something off in the basement.
I keep hearing children.
And Wati, I think she knows something.
-Take me there, Laras!
-I can't!
-Come on!
-I-I can't…Yuda, I can't!
I have to stay with Mom.
Laras…
What if it’s all true?
We know what it feels to lose someone.
It's okay…You can go!
I'm okay.
Laras, call Wati now!
Laras, is it here?
NO ENTRY
They’re all inside.
Wati!
Don't be noisy, let's go!
Take the body.
Take the soul, take the life.
Wah!
This gecko is not a sign
of misfortune…but fortune!
Eat!
Take the body, take the soul,
take the life.
We only need the children’s heads now.
Prepare yourself, now!
-Start your engine!
Start your engine!
That's the children!
Please, help!
Please! Help me!
That's the children!
Please, help!
Laras.
-Take the key, quick!
-Intan!
Intan!
Come on.
-Which one?
-Let me find it.
Intan!
Hurry, Yuda!
Hey.
Hey, don't make a noise!
I'll save you!
I'll save you, okay?
Come on.
Yuda! Intan is gone.
Let's find Intan!
Please stay here and I will go outside!
Let's go! Let's go!
Run, Run!
Yuda!
Hurry, Yuda!
How about them?
You guys can hide outside, okay?
Yuda, come on.
Take the body, take the soul.
Take the life.
Intan!
Don't screwed up!
Grab them all!
Let me go!
Let go!
Get off!
Intan, Intan!
Intan, Intan, wake up!
The children are gone, Sir!
What? Gone?
Yuda.
-Damn you!
-Yuda!
Why did you screw up this ritual?
Do you have any idea what you’ve done?
You bastard!
Those children are innocent--
They deserve to be free!
Child sacrifices are
our best option right now.
You don't understand…
How dangerous the unseen forces
at sea truly are!
Those workers are at risk…
Because of too many accidents.
Now there is no boundary between
the living world and the unseen…
Yuda! Yuda!
Yuda!
You, came this far just
to find your father, right?
Didn't you?
You really think
your father was a good man?
Rudi, bring him to me!
Bring me that kid!
Look carefully!
Look at him carefully!
He’s your stepbrother
from the woman I loved.
He’s your father’s child from an affair!
You'll be sorry!
Sir, there is disturbance on the coast!
What now?
Sir, it’s bad. Really bad!
Now what?
Everything on the ship has gone rotten!
Which one?
All of it, Sir! Rotten!
We’re doomed… we’ve been rejected!
What should we do then?
Sir.
Is there no other way?
They’re not going anywhere now!
No, there’s something more important now…
Let's go! Rudi, you stay here.
Come on.
-Follow me!
-Sure.
Children!
Mom!
I miss you.
Please accept my condolences, Wati!
We’re truly sorry!
I'm sorry, Wati!
You should stay strong, Wati!
-Mom!
Mom!
Mom?
You… son of a bitch!
-Mom!
Mom! Wahyu, just stay here!
-Laras?
Help! Help me!
Help!
Hey!
Damn it!
Let's go downstairs!
Help!
Mom, be careful! Mom!
Yuda!
Take the life.
Faithless humans!
Prepare yourselves
to become embers in hell!
Rudy, come on!
Rudi!
Faithless humans!
Prepare yourselves
to become embers in hell!
H-Help me!
Take the body,
take the soul, take the life.
Take the body, take the soul…
You die!
Our Father, we pray to You.
Protect us from all danger.
Our Father, who art in heaven,
hallowed be thy name, thy kingdom come…
thy will be done on earth
as it is in heaven.
Take the body, take the soul.
Take the life.
Mom!
-Mom!
Yuda!
This is what happens
when the ritual fails!
Happy now?
Mom, wake up!
Hey!
They’re all dead because of you!
Look! Look!
After this…
it will demand more sacrifices.
Maybe even your mother.
It is not you!
Or whatever thing you worship,
that decides who lives and dies!
Because of what you did…
innocent children became victims.
You’re the root of all this chaos!
They are demanding what was promised.
We must move fast
before the disaster grows.
Come on!
Handle this quietly.
Make sure it never reaches the media.
Mom, don't throw up your meal!
You want to drink first?
Mom, please eat just a bite of them.
Let me go!
Let me go! Mom!
Wahyu?
Where are you, Wahyu?
Wahyu!
Wahyu?
Take the body, take the soul.
Take the life.
Offer the sacrifice
for the safety of our lives!
Help!
No! Let me go!
Hey you!
Put it down!
I need a short video
for the report to the boss.
Sir…
Is it good?
We already agreed on what was promised.
But remember
this ritual’s success
is inseparable from the sacrifice.
It is bound to the seven elements
of the earth…
With vengeance as its flame.
So we must prepare offerings
for the coming nights of Suro.
What we agreed on must not be avoided.
Let's go!
Come on!
Where do your live?
Show me!
Where do you stay?
Open!
Open the door!
I’ve got your son, open up!
Open the door! Hey!
-Mom!
-Wahyu.
Mom!
Bayu!
He is truly a bastard!
What?
What are you looking for from my father?
How could he be used as a sacrifice?
Where were you?
-Where were you?
-I don't know!
Tell me!
I didn't even know it!
I didn't know!
I thought…
Bayu’s death was the most painful thing…
Turns out,
we both hurt each other just the same.
The moment I knew…
I am….the second wife,
who was never meant to exist.
You…don't ever…
Come to my life again.
Yuda! Yuda, please!
Please forgive me!
What do you mean all this time, Dad?
Damn it!
PORT
NO ENTRY
RESTRICTED AREA
I know why you’re trying
to ruin everything I’ve planned.
You and your sister…
One of you must become the sacrifice.
Hey!
We still need five more sacrifices.
And the executor must be someone
who carries vengeance toward
all seven targets.
Alright…
I'll be the executor.
As long as…
My mother and my sister stay alive.
Deal!
Mom, forgive me…
So, he is your stepbrother?
Finally you know about it.
It's been a long time.
I heard about the marriage.
But I didn’t have the heart to tell you.
I don't want you to hate your dad.
I didn’t have the heart to tell you.
I'm so sorry….
Wear this for the ritual.
Make sure before nightfall,
the entire construction area
is sterilized.
Whatever it takes, handle it immediately…
NO ENTRY
Hurry!
Hurry up…Hurry!
Block all access routes into the site.
Make the closure so no one can even peek.
-Understood!
-Go on!
-Do it!
-Yes, Sir!
Only we…
And them…
In full traditional attire….
Are permitted to enter.
Got it?
Yes, Sir!
Good job!
Wear this!
Mom!
Laras?
-What happened?
-I'm thirsty
-Thirsty?
-I'm thirsty.
Yes.
Mom, you can sit here first.
I'll get you some water.
Come, Mom.
Come on.
How long?
Thirsty…
Please, please wait!
Wait.
I want it more and more! I'm thirsty!
Here, Mom…Here!
You still thirsty?
Mom!
Jesus Christ, please help!
Mom?
Mom!
Please, Sir!
Yeah.
The living must be ready to die
and submit to power…
I grant you the dead
The living must be ready to die…
And submit to power
So the living may be spared…
With these sacrifices!
Saving us with these sacrifices!
Take the body, take the soul,
take the life.
-Mom!
-Take the body.
-Take the soul, take the life.
-Mom!
-Take the body, take the soul.
-Mom, please don't!
-Take the life.
Take the body, take the soul,
take the life.
Mom!
Snap out of it, Mom!
-Mom, snap out of it!
-Take the body, take the soul…
Come, Yuda.
Take the body, take the soul,
take the life.
Mom!
I'm really happy!
Yuda…come, come forward!
Mom…
Mom?
Mom!
Don’t be afraid, dear.
Come and join your dad.
Mom!
Now, she can be a mantis?
Ibu!
Yanto, please help my mom!
Rohman!
Hey!
Now get rid of it!
Hurry!
Hey!
Tomo!
Yanto!
Yanto, please find my mother!
Come on, Yanto!
-Mom!
-Your mother became a devil!
-Hurry!
-Calm, calm down!
-Don't panic! Don't panic!
-Come on!
Mom!
Damn it!
Rudi?
Yuda…I'm a friend of your father.
No, no.
Don't talk to Yuda.
Damn it!
Don't talk to Yuda. Talk to me.
You die, you die Sutomo!
-You die!
-You will!
Oh Rudi, how bad your fate is!
Ah… so much blood…
Yuda, please don't!
Yuda, I have a family.
Yuda, Yuda!
I also have mine!
Tomo, please help!
Hey!
Please don't, Tomo!
Tomo!
Please don't!
Don't be late, take the body!!
Hurry!
Hold on!
Let me calculate them all…
One, two, three, four,
Five, six…
Only six, Sir?
It should be seven right?
Yuda!
Where is the seventh one?
Sir, where is the other one?
Take the body, take the soul,
Take the life.
Mom!
Beneath the great bridge…
The sea keeps an old secret.
The souls of the sacrifices
are never at peace.
Like an infant… your father…
Who tried to stop
the offerings using your mother.
But the wrath of the sea goddess
could not be contained.
And in the end, he too became a servant
of the Eastern Sea Goddess.
A new project.